but right now it's time to play hallo
what
[Music]
the Halloween is nigh upon us but for a
certain breed of basement dwelling
weirdos on YouTube every day is an
excuse to dress up in a homemade
costume it's not
weird stop
it I'm going to show you a dressed up
creep on YouTube for 250 points you have
to give me their new catchphrase first
one this SpongeBob I assume he's not
wearing
pants F is for friends U is for you and
me and is for anywhere Under the
Sea Kevin Hey kids use my face as a
[Laughter]
[Applause]
toilet Jay hey kids I want you to touch
me under my sea yeah of
course next one this terrifying Gourmet
hello everyone it's fig abouton coming
to you with a candy
review oh it smells like um stinky
parmesan cheese you know like stinky fat
cheese that you put on your
pizza yes
Kevin I'm boy
Roseanne what an amazing
matchup Steve does this smell like
chloroform to
[Laughter]
you next one this lover of exploding
fruit
oh that
quickly is one of the most amazing
things I've ever
seen in my life yes Kevin banana
for
everyone
okay this is my elaborate ski to catch a
monkey and blow it
[Applause]
up